Guide to the Stanford Athletics Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford athletics photograph collection
1920s-1973
PC0010
Keeble, Richard.
17.13 Linear feet (47 volumes)
ca. 6900 photonegatives: nitrate and saftey.
The photographs, taken by professional photographers Richard Keeble and Glenn Kenyon, include action shots, formal group and team member photographs. While the concentration is on Stanford University's major sports--football, baseball, swimming and track--minor sports of both men's and women's athletics are also documented.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Richard Keeble, 1979.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
The photographs, taken by professional photographers Richard Keeble and Glenn Kenyon, include action shots, formal group and team member photographs. While the concentration is on Stanford University's major sports--football, baseball, swimming and track--minor sports of both men's and women's athletics are also documented.
Arrangement
Albums arranged chronologically by academic year; negatives arranged by negative number.
Access Terms
Keeble, Richard.; Kenyon, Glenn.; Stanford University. Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation.; Albums.; Photonegatives; Photoprints.
Collection Contents
- Photographs
  - 1930 (Box 1)
  - 1935 (Box 2)
  - 1946 (Box 3)
  - 1957 (Box 4)
  - 1920s (Box 5)
  - 1925, 1928, 1929, 1930-1931, 1936 (Box 6)
  - 1927, 1931-1932 (Box 7)
  - 1933, 1937 (Box 8)
  - 1947, 1948 (Box 9)
  - 1948, 1949 (Box 10)
  - 1949, 1950 (Box 11)
  - 1951, 1952, 1953, 1955 (Box 12)
  - 1953, 1954, 1958 (Box 13)
  - 1957, 1959, 1960 (Box 14)
  - 1961-1965 (Box 15)
  - 1966-1969 (Box 16)
  - 1969-1973 (Box 17)